Wow.
Amazing.
Lego ruins.
Look at that. Look at that.
Let's applaud!
Lego Market
The best issue book is ready!
Hey there!
I'm Satoshi Inagami from Sakurazaka 46. And where did I come from today?
Ta-da!
I've been to LEGOLAND! Yay!
I'm so excited! Those of you who know me already know that I love LEGO, and I've been wanting to come to LEGOLAND for a long time.
Yay!
I'm so excited!
I can't stop smiling.
Can I go now? I'll go as soon as I can.
I'm so excited.
Oh, man.
I'll get started.
Hello.
It's all LEGO.
Wow.
Isn't it amazing?
The whole wall is covered with
LEGO
This is the kind of world
This is what I wanted to come here.
Look at the welcome!
Ta-da!
Hello!Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
There's a friend of yours.
Ta-da!
Let's see if we can get a shot of that.
I see your friend's back.
I can see your friend's back.
Wow!
What's all this Lego?
Is that a Lego tower? Wait a minute.
Look.
What is this?
What is this? There's a man on it! Can you see it?
Ta-da! The people on this thing are amazing! It's so high!
Water on board!
So cute!
It's making noise.
Can you hear it? It's making a nice sound.
Can you hear that sound? Oh, my God!
Look at that!
Oh, my God!
They're so welcoming.
Oh, it stopped.
Whenever I go on an expedition, I always take my keychain with me.
I always take my keychain with me when I go on an expedition or something.
Which one should I take with me today?
I'll take the watermelon one! I'll take the angel one! I'll take the angel one!
I think about it a lot before I take them with me.
That's why I went abroad with Sakurazaka the other day.
I took an angel with me to Paris.When I was in Paris, I took an angel with me.
When I was in Malaysia, I took a Santa Claus and a cookie-shaped key chain, and one of them was a novelty item that you could get if you spent more than a thousand yen.
I got it because of something like that. That's why I'm attracted to limited editions.
What, what, what, what?
Wow, this is amazing!
Is that a ship?
Should I look at it from this side?
Oh, it's covered with water!
Wow! Oh, my gosh! Oh, it's splashing!
Oh, my gosh!
It took 2330 hours to make this.
I wonder who made it.
I applaud the person who made it.
That's amazing!
It's pouring water! There's some kind of attraction. I'd like to go in.
This is amazing!
I hear it's like the submarine we saw earlier. Like a boat.
I can get on it!
I can't stop smiling!
Okay, I'm off!
Oh, wow! I'm going on a submarine!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Here we go.
I see fish.
Can you see the Lego ruins, Lego ruins, Lego ruins, Lego ruins, Lego ruins
Lego ruins.
Ruins of LEGO
Lego ruinsLego Ruins
Lego Ruins
Lego RuinsLego Ruins
Look, look, look.
Isn't it amazing? It's in the ocean, right?
Oh, my God, it's huge.
That's a submarine.
Is this a restaurant? Look at this.
Look at the menu.
Look at this, huh? This is Nagoya's specialty, Hitsumabushi and Kaede!
I've been doing some research on my own, and this is the place I've been wanting to visit!
This is the place I've been wanting to visit!
This is it!
Minnie Land
I want to enter Minnie Land!
The pictures are amazing.
Wow, no, no, no, the pictures are amazing.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to show you... a highway... a real, real highway... and a real tree... right here.
There's a real highway here, a real highway, a real tree here, and a real tree here, and a real tree here, and a real tree here, and a real tree here.
Oh, my God.
This is gonna be hard to recognize.
Oh, this is a very familiar view.
I've walked here before.
Look, there's a button.
There's a bird!I got a bird.
That's great.
Can I try one more time?
Great, one more time, great, can you do this too?
Shibuya, the number, the notification is different, but you've seen it before, right?
Wow, I've been here too
Roppongi Hills, Tokyo Metropolitan Government...
And, oh...
On the other side, there's Fuji TV.
Fuji Television is located on that side.
What's this? It's a music video.
We had a music video, didn't we?
Buddies, right? We were filming, right?
No?
Buddies? Did you film it, members?
They used 10 million Legos in Miniland alone.
10 million.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I've checked it out, but the real thing is totally different.
The more you look at it, the more you realize how much LEGO was used.
Also, the level of reproduction is amazing!
I'm a little impressed.
There's something here!
They're on a date.
What's going on here?
That's amazing.
I'd like to go to a place where you can build your own Legos.
I'd like to go there.
Okay, I'll be right there.Well, I'll get right on it.
What can I make? Can I do it?
I was immediately greeted by LEGOs that everyone had made!
I'd like to make one based on the theme of Sakurazaka.
I don't know if I can do it well.
I always make things by looking at the instruction manual.
I'm going to try to make it with my own imagination.
Sakurazaka is also difficult, but I'm thinking of adding a little more pink and white.
I think I need a lot of blocks for this.
I've got a lot of blocks.
I'm trying to get a rough idea of what I want to do.
But I'm going to try my best to take pictures as I go along, and if I find something that's missing or not right, I'll put it back in.
I don't know what to do.
I've always loved fantasy.
I've always liked a lot of fantasy, and I've always wanted to be a wizard or something, but I can't imagine what it would be like...
I'm still not there yet, but I'm at 50%.
I'm 50% of the way there.
I'm still not there yet, but I'm 50%.
But you might not be able to do anything.
There's a possibility that we won't be able to do anything.
Time for LEGO has passed.
I'm afraid the time limit has come and gone.
The best problem solution in the LEGO market is ready!
Ta-da!
Let me see...
Let me explain.
I wanted to express cherry blossoms in various colors.
Sakurazaka members are members with various personalities, so I wanted to express them in various colors, and this is what I came up with.
This, ladies and gentlemen, is Buddies.
I put it on because I thought it was cute, which means I think you are all cute. I put it on because I thought it was cute, so it means that I think you are cute.I put it on because I thought it was cute, which means I think you're all cute. I put it on because I think it's cute, which means I think you're all cute.
The one that will be appreciated after I'm dead.
By the way, while I was making it, the manager was making it in the corner.
It's raining and it's raining and it's raining.
It's raining a little bit now, and we can't go on the rides because of the rain.
But I'm sure there's good food there.
It's starting to rain.
Oh!
You scared me! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You scared me.
That sounded amazing! You scared me!
I'm having some sweets.
This place seems to be very popular.
What is this place?
We've come to an amazing store.
Oh, thunder, the thunder was terrible.
What should I do?
I heard that the most popular item is the apple fry.
Ew.
I don't know what to do, but I want the most popular one.
I heard this is the most popular apple fry right now.
Have you ever had apple fries?
I don't think my fans know what I'm talking about.
I've been called an idiot.
I'm not so sure.
But since I'm here, I'd like to do a food report.
Look at this!
It's a cute little bego container.
I get excited when I see something like this, a cute container.I get excited about these things, cute little containers and all.
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
The apples are so sweet!
The food report and the radio broadcast were on the same time!
It's just like me, isn't it?
Let's try again!
Bon appétit!
I'm so excited!
It's raining so hard that every time I eat...
Something happens every time I eat.
It's a memory, isn't it?
I have to use my camera.
Oh, I'm at the store. I'm at a place called "The Big Shop".
I'm going to go to the big shop.
Legoland is so cute!
I'm gonna get a basket.
Let's fill it up.
Ta-da!
The feet light up.
I had this for a while.
But the arm came off, and it went away.
I want a new one.
I'll take this one.
I have a small key chain of this.
I'm going to buy a little light one.
Where is it? I don't know.
Oh! There it is!
This is what I was looking for.
You know, you can put mini-figures in this thing.You know, you can put mini-figures in this thing.
I've been looking for one of these for a long time.
I'll buy it.
I'll buy this one, I'll buy this one, I'll buy this one, I'll buy this one...
I'll buy this, I'll buy this, I'll buy this, I'll buy this.
You know what I'm talking about?
That's a shell.
They're cute.
Super cute.
Okay.
This is what I wanted.
I... I...
Wow, what should I do?
It's kind of tiny, too.
What?
But it's cute.
It's cute.
Look.
Isn't the navy color so cute?
Wow, I seriously don't know what to do.
I don't usually buy things like that.
I'll go with this one.
Heh heh heh heh heh
A day at LEGOLAND
A day at Legoland
But today was a little bit bad weather and rain, so we couldn't ride the attractions.
So next time I'll come with my members or something.
I would like to show you around Legoland.
Leave it to me, members!I'll leave it to you, all the members.
Thanks for watching today!
Lastly, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating and good button!
See you soon! Bye bye!
bye bye!